{
  "categories": [],
  "description": "Match the body part to these popular idioms.",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "questions": [{
    "answer": "foot",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Got off on the wrong ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "eyes",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "A sight for sore ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "hand",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "A bird in the ____ is worth two in the bush"
  }, {
    "answer": "Blood",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "_____ is thicker than water"
  }, {
    "answer": "ear",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "In one ___ and out the other"
  }, {
    "answer": "back",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "You scratch my ____, I'll scratch yours"
  }, {
    "answer": "teeth",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Through gritted _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "heart",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Cross one's _____ and hope to die"
  }, {
    "answer": "leg",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Shake a ___"
  }, {
    "answer": "stomach",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "The way to a man's heart is through his _______"
  }, {
    "answer": "knee",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "On bended ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "finger",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Five-______ discount"
  }, {
    "answer": "shoulder",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Have a chip on one's ________"
  }, {
    "answer": "hip",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Joined at the ___"
  }, {
    "answer": "mouth",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't look a gift horse in the _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "arm",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Long ___ of the law"
  }, {
    "answer": "fist",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Rule with an iron ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "throat",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Have a frog in one's ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "heads",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Two _____ are better than one"
  }, {
    "answer": "skin",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "There's more than one way to ____ a cat"
  }, {
    "answer": "Toe",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "___ the line"
  }, {
    "answer": "face",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Cut off your nose to spite your ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Nose",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "____ to the grindstone"
  }, {
    "answer": "neck",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Albatross around one's ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "chest",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Play one's cards close to the _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "side",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Thorn in one's ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "bone",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "As dry as a ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "wrist",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Slap on the _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "brow",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "By the sweat of one's ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "nerve",
    "category": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Strike a raw _____"
  }],
  "quizLength": 30,
  "title": "Body Part Cliches Quiz",
  "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/body-part-cliches-quiz.php"
}